德文
Devon!
不 听着 我们不开心 我们很痛苦
No. Listen, we're not happy, we're miserable.
伯特
Burt!
- 他们在地下折磨我们 - 德文
- They torture us down there! - Devon!
我们都是囚犯
We're prisoners!
伯特
Burt!
她还活着
She's alive!
- 是 好的 - 好
- Yeah. Okay. - Okay.
马克 来 你能抱她一会儿吗
Mark? Here. Will you take her for a second?
- 别担心 我会看着她 好的 - 小心点
- It's okay. I got her. Yeah. - Be careful with her.
- 但别走太远了 - 不会的
- Don't go far though. - I won't.
马克
Mark.
所以现在是你吗
So, this is you now?
是的
Yeah.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
是
Yeah.
- 你确定  - 是
- Are you sure? - Yeah.
我叫什么
What's my name?
波瑟芬妮
Persephone.
你能拼出来吗
Can you spell that?
- 不可能 - 好的
- Never. - Okay.
宝贝
Babe...
- 好的 - ...帮我弄弄尿布
- Okay. - ...need help with this diaper.
天啊
Oh, boy.
我觉得她想要妈咪了
I think she wants mommy.
恶心的娃
Fetid moppet.
父亲
Father.
我们会派分离层的人员 与员工外面的自己联络
We'll have someone from the floor liaise with the outies.
我们必须查出他们和谁聊过 越快越好
We need to find out who they talked to. Promptly.
你必须找到他们所有人
I need you to go see all of them.
查清他们说过什么话 和谁说的
Find out every word they said and who they said it to.
要辞退他们吗
And shall I fire them?
让基尔为你指引方向
Let Kier guide your hand.
是
Of course.
请坐
Please, sit.
我们已没收宾客拍摄的视频
We've commandeered the footage taken by guests.
娜塔莉已经开始与媒体沟通
Natalie is already doing outreach to media.
我们正在处理涉及此事的分离层员工
And the severed employees who were involved are being dealt with.
谢谢你的快速应对
Thank you for acting so quickly.
你帮我们避免了灾难
You saved us from disaster.
伊根先生会加入吗
Will Mr. Eagan be joining?
只有我
Just me.
我本人也应向你表示感谢
I personally owe you a debt of gratitude.
我为此付出了极大的代价
It cost me dearly.
的确
It did.
尽管如此 你在今晚证明了 自己对公司的忠诚
And still, you proved your loyalty tonight.
因此我们想重新聘请你
Which is why we'd like to ask you back.
你们应该道歉
An apology is warranted.
我向你道歉
I apologize.
我的父亲向你道歉
My father apologizes.
董事会向你道歉
The Board apologizes.
我们对待你非常不公
We've treated you poorly.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我接受你的道歉
I welcome your contrition.
那太好了
I'm so glad.
还有许多影响需要消除
There's much damage to control.
我建议从源头开始着手调查
I recommend we start by scouring the feed,
我需要对迪伦G问话 看看他是如何获得进入...
and I need to interview Dylan G. to see how he gained access to the--
我们在考虑另一件事
We have something else in mind.
我们想向你提供升职的机会
We'd like to offer you a promotion.
分离顾问委员会
Severance Advisory Council.
我从没听过这种组织
I never heard of such a thing.
这是全新的安排 你将领头创建这一委员会
It's a brand-new initiative. You'd be spearheading its formation.
公司非常重视你的才干
Your expertise is greatly valued.
所以应该由我担任分离层的主管
Which is why I should be running the severed floor.
米尔奇克先生已经升职为分离层经理
Mr. Milchick has been promoted to floor manager.
你们不器重我
You don't value me.
你们惧怕我
You fear me.
我们不惧怕任何人
We fear no one.
(治愈全人类的良药)
正因为我们如此看重你
And if we didn't hold you in such high esteem,
所以才会慷慨地向你提供这个机会
we wouldn't be making this generous offer.
我会考虑考虑的
I'll put some thought to it.
谢谢你抽空过来 哈蒙妮 达蒙德先生将送你出去
Thank you for coming in, Harmony. Mr. Drummond will see you out.
我不需要别人护送
I don't need an escort.
准备好了
Ready?
今天傍晚
Earlier this evening,
在一个晚宴上 我怀着激动的心情 作为已分离员工
at an event where I was excited to share my status as a severed individual
与朋友和合作伙伴们分享我的经历
with a group of friends and allies,
但我大意之下在发言前喝了酒
I made the poor decision to consume alcohol
且此前因为手臂起红疹 曾服用非卢蒙制的药物
while on a non-Lumon medication for an arm rash.
这导致我陷入酩酊状态
This had an inebriating effect,
继而发表了令我深感后悔的言论
which caused me to say some deeply regrettable things.
- 米尔奇克先生 - 抱歉我这么晚才来
- Mr. Milchick. - Apologies for the hour.
一切还好吗
Is everything all right?
你今晚过得怎么样 贝立夫先生
How's your night been, Mr. Bailiff?
挺好的 电视上正在播 《塞维利亚的理发师》
Fine. They're showing Barber of Seville on TV.
所以我正在家里看
So I've just been here.
真好 你感觉好吗
Wonderful. And you're feeling well?
天啊 我吃了什么
Oh, God. What did I eat in there?
我们只想知道有没有发生什么不寻常的事
We just need to know if anything of note occurred.
任何事
Anything at all.
米尔奇克先生 不如你说说 发生了什么事吧
Why don't you tell me what's going on, Mr. Milchick?
当时 我以为自己很幽默
In the moment, I thought I was being funny.
但在鲁莽的发言之后
But in the hours since this outburst,
我想起我家族的公司
I've been reminded just how seriously my family's company
在世界各地人民的生活中 有多么深远的影响
affects the lives of real people around the world.
你知道 你公司里的自己和我是朋友
You know, your innie is a friend of mine.
我相信他也会同意我这么说的
I feel confident he'd approve of me saying so.
他是一个有原则的人 这很难得
And he's a man of principle, which is rare.
所以这真的是一个艰难的决定
Which is what makes this so difficult.
你要辞退我
You're firing me?
卢蒙遇到问题时
When Lumon falters,
总是我们最珍惜的员工 和他们的家人首当其冲受伤害
it's our cherished workers and their families who suffer first.
对于这所造成的恐惧和不安 我深切致歉
So for the fear and insecurity this has caused, I must sincerely atone.
你在今天傍晚
You were involved in a physical altercation
与另一名员工起了肢体冲突
with another employee this evening.
虽然短暂但是存在暴力
It was brief but violent.
很遗憾 你是施暴者
And I regret to say that you were the aggressor.
- 等等... - 因此
- Wait-- - As such,
我们不得不终止与你的雇佣关系
I'm afraid we've no choice but to terminate your employment,
即刻生效
effective immediately.
令人难过的是 对卢蒙的不信任 自从公司初创以来就广泛存在
Distrust of Lumon has been sadly endemic since its founding.
我的言论滋长了恶毒的仇恨和嘲笑
My words provided more fuel for a pernicious hate and derision.
你不能说炒人就炒 到底发生了什么
You can't just do that. What happened?
我弄坏了什么东西吗 还是... 我可以赔钱的 我楼上有现金
Did I break something? Or I can pay. I have cash upstairs.
我说公司里的自己被折磨...
When I said my innie was being tortured...
我该怎么和妻子解释
What am I supposed to tell my wife?
那是个玩笑 也是个谎言
This was a joke and a lie.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我由内至外都忠诚于本公司
I'm committed to this company with every part of me.
但我同时也是一个人
But I'm also human.
和我公司里的自己一样
Just like my innie...
也和你一样
and just like you.
人生切割术
第二季 第二集
这比我计划的要跌宕起伏得多
Well, that was more drama than I planned.
是吧
I guess so.
下次再举行读书会时我会通知你
I'll let you know if we do another reading.
好 一定告诉我
Yes, please do.
你也别责怪宝宝 里肯 那不是她的错
And don't punish the baby, Ricken. This wasn't its fault.
当然不是 晚安 瑞贝卡
Of course. Good night, Rebeck.
不止我一人听到你那么说
I'm not the only one who heard you say it.
- 这可不是我编出来的 - 是 其实 我就是...
- It's not like I made this up. - Right. You know, I'm just--
我们可以将读书会改到下个月 没事的
We can reschedule the reading to next month. It's fine.
我只是要决定是否要从第一章
I just have to decide if I'm going to restart
- 开始重读 - 所以呢
- with chapter 1. - So what?
你说“她还活着”
So you said, "She's alive."
- 别介意我... - 我是想帮你
- If I may-- - I'm trying to help you.
别介意我插嘴 我个人觉得你显然是在说宝宝
If I may, I really did feel it was clear you were referencing the baby.
- 巴顿救了她 - 他找到了她 没错
- Patton had just saved her. - Well, he found her, yeah.
我觉得你公司里的自己很激动
And I think that your workie was excited.
不得不说 马克 他很优秀
I have to say, Mark, he really is a jewel.
两位 我显然是在说宝宝
Guys, obviously I was referencing the baby.
是
Yeah.
- 好吗  - 是
- Okay? - Yes.
不 对 我同...我觉得里肯说得对
No. Yeah. I agre... I think Ricken is right.
我同意
I agree.
我...宝贝 你能抱她一会儿吗
I... Babe, will you take her for a second?
好
Yep.
我们来将整件事剥丝抽茧吧
So let's Occam's razor this shit.
你在找埃莉诺
You're looking for Eleanor,
你发现了一张照片 显然对其产生了兴趣
you find this picture, which obviously is of interest to you,
- 所以你拿起照片 - 是
- so you pick it up. - Right.
然后 当巴顿找到埃莉诺...
And then when Patton found Eleanor--
- 我还是得纠正下 是救了她 - 好 随便 对
- Saved her, I'd still say. - Okay, whatever, yes.
- 你仍然拿着照片 - 对
- You still had it with you. - Yeah.
是 我觉得只有这样才说得通
Yeah. I think it's the only thing that makes sense.
好吧 埃莉诺在书房 因为...
Okay. And Eleanor was in the study because...
因为塞尔维格太太把她放在那里了
Because Mrs. Selvig left her in there.
- 或科贝尔 谁知道 - 是
- Or Cobel, whatever the fuck. - Right.
我建议叫她“科贝尔维格”
Perhaps "Cobelvig" would be a helpful nomenclature.
假定“她还活着”真的是在说宝宝
And assuming that "She's alive" really was about the baby--
你觉得不是吗
I mean, you don't think it was?
- 我觉得是 - 那你为什么这种语气
- I do think it was. - Then why are you saying it like that?
我没...抱歉 我只是太累了
I don't... Sorry, I'm just exhausted.
- 今晚真的很奇怪 马克 - 天啊
- It's been a weird fucking night, Mark. - Oh, my God.
你干吗现在
Why are you getting aggressive
- 一直怼我  - 我的天 这...
- with me right now? - Oh, my God! Th--
- 好了 两位 别这样... - 随你
- Okay, guys. Okay. - Whatever.
我们来说说已知事实 好吗
Let's deal with what we know to be true, all right?
马克工作时的自己想方设法醒过来 提醒我们公司存在虐待
Mark's workie went to great lengths to awaken himself to alert us to abuses.
他是受了我的书启发
He was inspired by my book.
他在书中找到了巨大的意义 深刻
He found great meaning in it. Profundity.
要我命 瑞贝卡
Goddamn it, Rebeck.
- 亲爱的 你能...抱抱她吗  - 好
- Honey, can-- Got her? - Yeah.
你到底在说什么
What the fuck are you even saying?
你干吗对我这么混账 我是在帮你
Why are you being a dick to me? I'm trying to help you.
- 我只是想要... - 晚上好 黑尔博士
- I'm just trying to get-- - Good evening, Dr. Hale.
- 晚上好 - 我是卢蒙的塞斯米尔奇克
- Good evening. - Seth Milchick from Lumon.
不知道马克斯科特是否在这
Is Mark Scout here by chance?
他在
Yes, he is.
请进
Come in.
谢谢
Thank you.
斯科特先生
Mr. Scout.
我猜你此刻有一些疑问
I imagine you have a few questions.
可以这么说
You could say that.
能坐下来聊聊吗
May I sit with you?
这边请
Right this way.
你一定就是德文
You must be Devon.
好的 那么
Okay. So...
这个头盔非常华丽
That is a magnificent helmet.
谢谢
Thank you.
今晚的事是我们所说的“紧急加班”
What happened tonight is what we call the "overtime contingency."
这是公司的安全措施
It's a safeguard we employ
用于处理需在公司外的地方 联络到你工作人格的情况
if we ever need to access your work personage off company grounds.
是 你们没和我说过这个
Yeah, you never told me about this.
你的入职文件中有紧急加班披露资料
OTC disclosure can be found in your start paperwork.
似乎你的一位同事操控了公司中的技术
It seems the tech was commandeered by one of your office mates,
他因此让你们其余三人苏醒了39分钟
allowing him to wake the rest of you for a period of 39 minutes.
公司里的马克曾来过这个家
Innie Mark was here in this house.
我知道 我和他聊过
I know. I talked to him.
他对你说了什么
What did he say to you?
如果我告诉你 你会为此惩罚他吗
If I tell you, are you gonna punish him for it?
卢蒙不会惩罚员工
We have no punishments at Lumon.
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
我们更关心你的状态 斯科特先生
We're more concerned about how you're doing, Mr. Scout.
我能想象你一定因为 他的行为而感到备受侵犯
I can only imagine how violated you feel by his actions.
- 说到侵犯... - 你...
- Yes, speaking of violations... - You--
我只是好奇
...just wondering how common it is
管理人员冒充母乳专家 干涉员工家庭
for your managers to commit fucking lactation fraud
这种事在贵公司常见吗
against their employees' families.
挺常见
Pretty common?
科贝尔女士
Ms. Cobel.
对
Yeah.
我们今晚得知她的状态极度不正常
What we learned tonight is that she is quite severely unwell.
可不是 她是我隔壁邻居
Yeah. She lives next door to me.
我认识她
I, like, know her.
她在卢蒙的行为
And her behavior at Lumon
似乎正是你公司里的自己痛苦的原因
seems to be the source of your innie's distress.
她再也不会下到那一个楼层了
She will never descend to that floor again.
也不会再在公司外为你带来更多损害
Nor bedevil you out here any further.
我向你保证
You have my word.
但我们必须查清目前的问题在哪
But we do need to know what we're dealing with.
有什么你可以告诉我的吗
Is there anything? Anything you can tell me?
这...
I mean--
没有 我们都很累了
No, I mean, we're very tired.
是的 很累
Yes, we are.
我觉得 要说的话我们刚都说了
I think we've just said all there is to say.
好的 没问题 我之后会再跟进
Okay. Of course. I'll circle back.
在那之前 希望周一在公司见到你
In the meantime, I hope to see you Monday.
是 那很难说 哥们
Yeah. I don't know, man.
你公司里的自己今晚所做的事 是完全未经授权的
What your innie did tonight was completely unauthorized.
同时 也很勇敢
It was also very brave.
我不希望他的勇气换来的是被抹杀
I'd hate to reward his courage with nonexistence.
(伯特古德曼)
你认为我们是否即将遇到各自的伴侣
You think we're about to meet our spouses?
也许吧
Maybe.
也许正是彼此呢
Maybe it's each other.
那就太有趣了
That'd be a hoot.
对 也许正在因为洗车优惠券争吵
Yeah, like, mid-argument over car wash coupons.
“亲爱的 你把优惠券剪错了”
"Honey, you're cutting them wrong!"
- 好了 - 好
- Okay. - All right.
以防我们回不来
In case we don't come back.
不知道 也许是以防我们能回来
Or, I don't know, in case we do?
以防我们回不来
In case we don't come back.
不知道 也许是以防我们能回来
Or, I don't know, in case we do?
(会很好玩的 我保证)
(我知道)
(昨晚好奇怪 我能给你带点难吃的外卖吗 )
(优门)
你能行的
You got this.
不用有压力 淡定
No pressure. Be cool.
你最优秀了 笑一笑
You are so awesome. Smile.
我可以问问公司有什么福利吗
May I ask about benefits?
有一台咖啡机
There's a coffee maker.
我指的是医疗福利
I meant health care benefits.
当然 好的 你和你家人都享有
Sure. Yes, of course. For you. Your family.
好的 太好了 你知道
Okay, great. Yeah, you know,
我认为这个职位 真的非常适合我 萨利巴先生
I think this is gonna be a really great fit for me, Mr. Saliba.
你知道 我从小
You know, ever since I was a kid,
- 就觉得门特别... - 多大
- I've always felt like doors had-- - How old?
不好意思 什么
Sorry?
你多大的时候发现自己喜欢门
How old were you when you knew you loved doors?
五岁
Five.
如果你能成为任何一种门 你想成为哪种
If you could be any kind of door, what would it be?
滑动门
Pocket.
- 有趣 解释一下吧 - 好
- Interesting. Tell me more. - Yes.
平时我就是一扇门 履行门的责任 然后
Well, you're, you know, doing your door thing and then
不需要门的时候 我可以...
when you're not needed, you can just--
默默滑走
Just tuck yourself away.
哑光还是蛋壳光
Flat finish or eggshell?
半亮光
Semi-gloss.
性感
That's hot.
你让我想起了自己 迪伦
You remind me of me, Dylan.
你喜欢踢球吗
You like kickball?
是问我会不会踢球 还是问我追不追联赛 我...
As a skill? Or, like, do I follow it professionally? I--
对
Yeah.
我们每周五有足球比赛 如果赢的话 会有好玩的奖品
We play on Fridays. There's a fun prize if you win.
你是说“入门奖”
You mean a door prize.
抱歉 烂梗
Sorry.
你打过很多短期工 然后入职了卢蒙
A lot of short-term employment. And then Lumon.
- 是的 - 他们的门都是内部制造的
- Yes. - And they make their doors in-house.
真够自大的
It's fucking hubris.
对
Yeah.
我是分离层员工 所以...
I was a severed employee, so...
你是分离层员工
You're a severed?
是 对的 但你知道
Yes. Yeah, I was. But you know,
我不是他...
it's just me here and...
乔治先生 多谢你今天来面试
Well, Mr. George, thanks for coming in.
什么
What?
我们会全面考虑你的申请
We'll consider your application thoroughly.
就这样 只因为我曾分离
That's it? Just because I'm severed?
像我说的 我们会全面考虑你的申请
Like I said, we'll consider your application thoroughly.
好吧 你们完全不会考虑请我 这是歧视
Okay. You're not considering me at all. That's discrimination.
我们公司需要的是 某种特定人才 乔治先生
We need a certain kind of person here, Mr. George,
而不是某种特定的两个人才
not a certain kind of two people.
你觉得这里是地毯工厂吗
What do you think this is? A carpet factory?
- 什么  - 你想做大脑包皮切割术
- What? - You want to circumcise your brain,
那是你的决定
that's your business.
但那不意味着我必须雇用你 我个人对分离厌恶至极
But it doesn't mean I have to hire you. And personally, I think it's abhorrent.
你稍微想想
Read the room.
如果是好消息 我肯定会接电话的嘛
I would have picked up the phone if it was good news.
抱歉 下一个一定可以的
I'm sorry. You'll get the next one.
别对我这么好了
Stop being nice.
嘿 家里还有没有宝宝湿巾
Hey, do we need more baby wipeys?
应该有
I don't think so.
这样吧 我还是买点回去 我很快回家
You know what? I'll get some anyway. I'll be home soon.
好的 拜拜 亲爱的
Okay. Bye, hon.
所以 他是你上司
So, he's your boss?
“科贝尔维格”呢 你有她的消息吗
And what about "Cobelvig"? Have you heard from her?
我去过她家 但没人应门
I went by there. No one answered the door though.
该死 我在想
Fuck. Well, I was just thinking,
也许我们有办法确认 你公司里的自己说的是什么意思
maybe there was a way we could confirm what your innie meant.
德文 我的天 你是认真的吗
Devon. Jesus Christ. Are you serious?
我知道我们不应该联络他
I know we're not supposed to contact him
但丹尼斯是律师 据她说
but Danise is a lawyer and apparently,
- 你可以申请... - 我要辞职
- you can petition-- - I'm quitting.
- 你要辞职  - 对
- You're quitting? - Yeah.
好吧 你打给公司了吗
Okay. Have you called them already?
不 我打算今晚提出来
No, I was gonna do it tonight.
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你不是从我入职以来就一直要我辞职吗
Haven't you been trying to get me to quit that place since I got there?
我以为这么做 我是终于满足了你的心愿
I thought I was finally doing what you want.
不 是没错 但你不觉得 昨晚的事很古怪吗
No. Yes, but don't you think that was strange last night?
你想想 他为什么那么想知道
I mean, why was he so curious?
德文 你在干吗  你记得我做过家属辨认 对吧
Devon, what are you doing? You remember I identified her, right?
- 是的 马克 - 我看到她的尸体了
- Yes, Mark. - I saw her body.
对 我知道
Yeah, I know.
我的问题是 如果我们能再获得一点确认
My thing is, if we could just get, like, a half-step more confirmation,
那以后就不会总为这件事纠结了
then it's not gonna be something that continues to haunt us.
- 你懂吗  - 我们
- Do you know what I mean? - Us?
对 她也是我的家人 马克 要命
Yes. She was my family too, Mark. Fuck.
对 但她是我的妻子
Yeah. But she was my wife.
我知道 但她的死影响的不只是你
I know, but you're not the only one her death affected.
- 真的 也影响了你  - 对
- Oh, really? It affected you? - Yes.
是你必须去通知她父母她身亡了吗
Did you have to tell her parents that she was dead?
还有她的学生
How about her students?
还有
How about this.
那之后 你的床单有她的气味 几周都不散吗
Did your sheets smell like her for weeks afterwards?
你知道吗 说实话 如果里肯死了 他的尸体火化了
You know what? Honestly, if Ricken died and his body burned,
- 我会为你难过 - 天
- I'd be sad for you. - Wow.
但我不会受影响
But I wouldn't be affected.
你的话太荒唐了
This is obscene.
我只是想确定
I just want to be sure.
我很确定
I am sure!
- 回头聊 - 马克
- I'll talk to you later. - Mark.
马克
Mark.
(皮普烧烤店)
(嬉笑)
(欢迎来到利奥诺拉湖公寓)
(电话亭)
好的
Okay.
你不接电话 我懂
You're not picking up. I get it.
我希望你知道我公司里的自己 收到你的讯息了
I want you to know my innie got the message.
(卢蒙)
米尔奇克先生
Mr. Milchick?
公司的礼物
Compliments of the company.
昨晚我没能给你留下好印象
We got off on the wrong foot last night.
可以简短地聊聊吗
Okay to talk a minute?
好 进来吧
Yeah. Come on in.
谢谢
Thank you.
斯科特先生 我知道 你仍然在考虑是否回卢蒙工作
So, Mr. Scout, I know you're still weighing whether to return to Lumon.
对
Yeah.
我想问你几个问题 这可能会影响你的决定
I'd like to ask you a few questions that may inform your decision.
可以吗
Is that all right?
好
Okay.
很好
Terrific.
首先 你对目前的薪酬待遇满意吗
First, how happy are you with your current financial compensation?
这么问是因为如果你决定回公司
I ask because our endearment to you is such that a 20% bump is on the table,
我们愿考虑加薪20%
should you return.
20% 天
20%. Wow.
第二个问题是 对你公司里的自己声称的事
My second question is whether a full investigation into your innie's claims,
进行全面调查 以及独立机构的定期健康检查
and regular wellness checks from independent orgs,
会不会让你更想要回到公司
would help you feel more excited to return?
我不知道 公司打算这样做吗
Well, I don't know. Is that what they're doing?
这是众多举措中的第一步
It's the first step of many.
第三个问题与你的亡妻珍玛有关
My third question concerns your late wife, Gemma.
和她怎么有关
What about her?
在你的入职访问中
In your intake interview,
你提到她的死是你选择分离的主要原因
you cited her death as a primary motivator for severing.
你记得你当时说了什么吗
Do you remember what you said?
不记得
No.
你说自从她死后 每过一天感觉都像一年
You said since she died, every day feels like a year.
你觉得她的死让你一直如鲠在喉
That you felt like you were choking on her ghost.
斯科特先生 你仍是这样感觉吗
Do you still feel that way, Mr. Scout?
我在卢蒙所认识的马克很快乐
The Mark I've come to know at Lumon is happy.
他在乎身边的人 他很幽默
He cares for people and he's funny.
他不知道我眼前的你所展现出的这种痛苦
He knows nothing of the pain I see in you right now.
他找到了爱
He's found love.
爱
Love?
和谁
With who?
你让他在地下寻找到慰藉 最终那也会反馈到你身上的
The solace you have given him down there will make its way to you.
假以时日即可
It just takes time.
我希望你愿意给我们时间 斯科特先生
I hope you'll give us that time, Mr. Scout.
(卢蒙 马克斯科特)
你们满意吗
Are you satisfied with this?
他妹妹看起来比他傲慢
The sister seems more uppity than he is.
你打算让谁进宏观数据精检部
So, who are you bringing into MDR?
我有一个从海外调来的灵活调配员工 还有两个被5X裁员的
I've got a floater from overseas and a pair who were laid off from 5X.
5X
5X?
真的
Really?
我只有48小时来安排好一切
I had 48 hours to pull this together.
希望他们之间会有化学反应
Hopefully there will be some chemistry.
(卢蒙 达里奥罗西)
我们不需要化学反应
We don't need chemistry.
我们需要马克S回来工作
We need Mark S. back to work.
上楼吧
Go on ahead.
他需要待到冷港完成
Long enough to complete Cold Harbor.
- 今晚见 - 好
- See you tonight. - All right.
- 晚安 斯科特先生 - 晚安 贾德
- Good night, Mr. Scout. - Good night, Judd.
早上好 斯科特先生
Good morning, Mr. Scout.
早上好 贾德
Morning, Judd.
- 晚安 斯科特先生 - 晚安 贾德
- Good night, Mr. Scout. - Night, Judd.
早上好 斯科特先生
Good morning, Mr. Scout.
早上好 贾德
Good morning, Judd.
- 斯科特先生 - 晚安 贾德
- Mr. Scout. - Good night, Judd.
喂 有人吗 董事会在吗
Hello? Is anyone there? Is the Board on?
我是宏观数据精检部的马克S
It's Mark S. from Macrodata Refinement.
好吧 如果你们在 请听我说
Okay. Well, if you're there, please listen.
我知道你们想要公正地对待 记忆分离的人们
Now, I know that you want to do the right thing for severed people,
- 所以你们必须再让我见我的团队 - 马克
- which is why I need to see my team again. - Mark!
如果像你们说的 我们真的是分离改革的带路人
If we truly are the face of severance reform, as you say,
- 那就应该给他们一个机会 - 马克
- then they deserve a chance. - Mark!
拜托了 他们是我的朋友 你们不能就这样让他们消失
Please. They're my friends! You can't just make them disappear!
当然 我承担全部责任
Of course, I bear full responsibility.
董事会将满足他的要求
The Board's gonna give him what he wants,
包括赫莉R
including Helly R.
没有他们 他是不会完成任务的
He won't finish without them.
米尔奇克先生
Mr. Milchick?
乔治先生
Mr. George.
这种事闻所未闻
This is unheard of.
- 抱歉 威尔金斯先生 - 上了三天班
- I'm sorry, Mr. Wilkins. - Three days of work.
我为此中止了大急流城的租约
I broke a fucking lease in Grand Rapids.
别碰我
Fucking touch me.
否则我上诉就多了一条理由
Give me another reason to sue.
去你的 卢蒙
Fuck you, Lumon!
嗨 贾德
Hey, Judd.
早上好 贾德
Morning, Judd.
嘿
Hey!
嗨 马克 刚下班
Hello, Mark. Just back from work?
你要去哪
Where do you think you're going?
和你有什么关系
What do you care?
和我有什么关系
What do I care?
和我有...
What do I c--
你是谁
Who are you?
我以为你要辞职
I thought you were quitting.
我曾信任你
I trusted you.
我把过去两年的经历告诉了你
I told you what I'd gone through these past two years.
你...
You...
你擅闯我家 你...
You were in my house. You...
我吃过你的烂曲奇
I ate your shitty fucking cookies.
他们说服你留下了
They convinced you to stay?
送了你黄梨果篮
Was a pineapple involved?
你真好哄
You're so easy to sway.
什么 就这样 你就...这么走了
What? So that's it? You're just... You're leaving?
你是在逗我...
Are you fucking kid--
你为什么这么做 这一切到底怎么回事
Why did you do this? What the fuck is this all about?
关于珍玛 你知道些什么吗
Do you know something about Gemma?